angel-jobs.com 2017-04-15

# 

## Introduction

We, at **Angel-Jobs.com** value the privacy of its user and are committed to respect your need for appropriate protection and management of any personally identifiable information inclusive of first name, last name, home or other physical address and an email address or other contact information, whether at work or at home but not limited to. With a view to offer most enriching and holistic internet experience to its users, Angel-Jobs.com is too stringent in concealing all the personal information that you share with us.

By utilizing our website or its services, in either case by logging or registering, you consent to collection, storage, and use of the personal information you provide (including any changes thereto as provided by you) for any of the services that we offer.

## Personal Information

To avail our services, users will have to provide certain information for the registration process viz.:- a) name, b) email address, c) sex, d) age, e) PIN code , f) credit card or debit card details, g) password, h) your occupation, interests, likes etc. The information supplied by the users enables us to fetch you the best opportunities and provide you the most user-friendly experience. All required information is wholly service dependent and they are required to maintain, protect, and improve its services and for developing new services.

Such information will not be considered as sensitive if it is freely available and accessible in the public domain or is furnished under the Right to Information Act, 2005 or any other law for the time being in force.

## Credit Check and Fraud Prevention

We use standard and authorized payment services and our Credit Check and Fraud Prevention policies are aligned to these companies. All disputes would be handled by Mumbai courts.

## Third Party Services

We provide certain services where we are bound to link to third-party service providers (links to other websites) who help us to deliver programs, products, information, and services. Such sites are governed by their respective privacy policies, which are beyond our control. Hence, we do not assure you to disguise your personal or user information as their policy may differ from ours. Once you leave our servers (you can tell where you are by checking the URL in the location bar on your browser), use of any information you provide is governed by the privacy policy of the operator of the site you are visiting. If you can't find the privacy policy of any of these sites via a link from the site's homepage, you should contact the site directly for more information. When we present information to our advertisers -- to help them understand our audience and confirm the value of advertising on our website -- it is usually in the form of aggregated statistics on traffic to various pages within our site.

We may pass your details to other companies in our group. We may also pass your details to our agents and subcontractors to help us with any of our uses of your data set out in our Privacy Policy. For example, we may use third parties to assist us with delivering products to you, to help us to collect payments from you, to analyze data and to provide us with marketing or customer service assistance. We may exchange information with third parties for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction. We may transfer our databases containing your personal information if we sell our business or part of it. Other than as set out in this Privacy Policy, we shall NOT sell or disclose your personal data to third parties without obtaining your prior consent unless this is necessary for the purposes set out in this Privacy Policy or unless we are required to do so by law. The Site may contain advertising of third parties and links to other sites or frames of other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices or content of those third parties or other sites, nor for any third party to whom we transfer your data in accordance with our Privacy Policy.

## Confidentiality and Security

  1. We take appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of data. These include internal reviews of our data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures, including appropriate encryption and physical security measures to guard against unauthorized access to systems where we store personal data.
  2. All information gathered on Angel-Jobs.com is securely stored within Angel-Jobs.com controlled database. The database is stored on servers secured behind a firewall; access to the servers is password-protected and is strictly limited. However, as effective as our security measures are, no security system is impenetrable. We cannot guarantee the security of our database, nor can we guarantee that information you supply will not be intercepted while being transmitted to us over the Internet. And, of course, any information you include in a posting to the discussion areas is available to anyone with Internet access.
  3. We limit access to personal information about you to employees who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs.
  4. We have physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with the laws prevalent in India to protect personal information about you. We seek to ensure compliance with the requirements of the Information Technology Act, 2000 and Rules made there under to ensure the protection and preservation of your privacy.
  5. We restrict access to your personally identifying information to employees who need to know that information in order to operate, develop or improve our services.
  6. Information or materials on this website is entirely at your own risk.
  7. **Angel-Jobs.com** will not contact children under age 13 about special offers or for marketing purposes without a parent's permission. 

## Cookies

The acceptance of cookies is not a requirement for visiting the Site. However we would like to point out that the some functionality on the Site and ordering is only possible with the activation of cookies. Cookies are tiny text files which identify your computer to our server as a unique user when you visit certain pages on the Site and they are stored by your Internet browser on your computer's hard drive. Cookies can be used to recognize your Internet Protocol address, saving you time while you are on, or want to enter, the Site. We only use cookies for your convenience in using the Site (for example to remember who you are when you want to amend your shopping cart without having to re-enter your email address) and not for obtaining or using any other information about you (for example targeted advertising). Your browser can be set to not accept cookies, but this would restrict your use of the Site. Please accept our assurance that our use of cookies does not contain any personal or private details and are free from viruses. If you want to find out more information about cookies, go to [http://www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/)or to find out about removing them from your browser, go to <http://www.allaboutcookies.org/manage-cookies/index.html>.

The Site uses technology from Google Analytics through which data is collected and stored for marketing and optimization purposes and data use profiles are prepared under a pseudonym. Cookies may be used for this. The cookies enable recognition of the Internet browser. The data collected with these technologies is not used, without separate authorization by the person concerned, to personally identify the visitors to this website and is not collated with personal data on the pseudonym holder. The permission for data recording and storage may at any time be cancelled with on-going effect

## Access and Updation of Your Personal Information

  1. We provide mechanisms for updating and correcting your personally identifying information as and when requested by you, with access to your personal information and shall further ensure that any personal information or sensitive personal data or information found to be inaccurate or deficient shall be corrected or amended as feasible, subject to any requirement for such personal information or sensitive personal data or information to be retained by law or for legitimate business purposes.
  2. We ask individual users to identify themselves and the information requested to be accessed, corrected or removed before processing such requests, and we may decline to process requests that are unreasonably repetitive or systematic, require disproportionate technical effort, jeopardize the privacy of others, or would be extremely impractical (for instance, requests concerning information residing on backup tapes), or for which access is not otherwise required. In any case where we provide information access and correction, we perform this service free of charge, except if doing so would require a disproportionate effort.
  3. Because of the way we maintain certain services, after you delete your information, residual copies may take a period of time before they are deleted from our active servers and may remain in our backup systems.

## Allocation and Disclosure of Information

**Angel-Jobs.com** does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people (save with your consent) or non-affiliated companies except to provide products or services you've requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances

  1. We provide the information to trusted partners who work with Angel-Jobs.com under confidentiality agreements. These companies may use your personal information however these companies do not have any independent right to share this information.
  2. We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims when it is requested or required by law or by any court or governmental agency or authority to disclose, for the purpose of verification of identity, or for the prevention, detection, investigation including cyber incidents, or for prosecution and punishment of offences. These disclosures are made in good faith and belief that such disclosure is reasonably necessary for enforcing these Terms; for complying with the applicable laws and regulations.
  3. We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of Angel-Jobs.com terms of use, or as otherwise required by law.
  4. We transfer information about you if Angel-Jobs.com is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, Angel-Jobs.com will notify you before your personal information is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

## Updating of Privacy Policy

However the internet is a dynamic process, Angel-Jobs.com reserves the right to update, change or modify the privacy policy from time to time to incorporate necessary future changes. Obviously, our use of any information we gather, will always be consistent with the policy under which the information was collected, regardless of what the new policy may be.

## Disclaimer

**Angel-Jobs.com** does not store or keep credit card data in a location that is accessible via the Internet. Once a credit card transaction has been completed, all credit card data is moved off-line only to ensure that the data/credit card information received is not accessible to anyone after completion of the on-line transaction and to ensure the maximum security. 

**Angel-Jobs.com** shall not be liable for any loss or damage sustained by reason of any disclosure (inadvertent or otherwise) of any information concerning the user's account and/or information relating to or regarding online transactions using credit cards/debit cards and/or their verification process and particulars nor for any error, omission or inaccuracy with respect to any information so disclosed and used whether or not in pursuance of a legal process or otherwise.

## Contact Information

**Angel-Jobs.com** invites your comments regarding this privacy statement at the contact address given at the website. Should there be any concerns about contravention of this Privacy Policy, Angel-Jobs.com will employ all commercially reasonable efforts to address the same.

We request you to please provide the following information in your complaint:-

  1. A physical or electronic signature of a person authorized to act on behalf of the copyright owner for the purposes of the complaint
  2. Identification of the copyrighted work claimed to have been infringed.
  3. Identification of the material on our website that is claimed to be infringing or to be the subject of infringing activity.
  4. The address, telephone number or e-mail address of the complaining party
  5. A statement that the complaining party has a good-faith belief that use of the material in the manner complained of is not authorized by the copyright owner, its agent or the law.
  6. A statement, under penalty of perjury, that the information in the notice of copyright infringement is accurate, and that the complaining party is authorized to act on behalf of the owner of the right that is allegedly infringed.

**Note :** The terms in this agreement may be changed by Angel-Jobs.com at any time and is free to offer its services to any client/prospective client without restriction.
